naijadailies.com 2019-06-29

# Naija Dailies: Privacy Policy

The NaijaDailies.com website is maintained by 

**Zeemfa LTD.**

NaijaDailies.com collects personally identifying information and data about individuals, their company, and the companies demographics (“personally identifying information and data”) including (i) when you provide information to NaijaDailies.com, such as when you register or sign up for any of our services such as forum discussions and other communications with NaijaDailies.com, (ii) when you register or sign up on the NaijaDailies.com site or when you register for any other Zeemfa’ online services, your information will be known to NaijaDailies.com and (iii) from time to time we may add other information that we collect from third party sources to enhance the information that you provided to NaijaDailies.com. 

Below is the current policy regarding the usage of personally identifying information and data collected by NaijaDailies.com. We re-evaluate this policy on an ongoing basis based on feedback from readers. **NaijaDailies.com** reserves the right to change its privacy policy. However, if there are any changes to the use of personally identifying information and data that is different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify you by posting a notice on our website. 

NaijaDailies.com or one of our Zeemfa affiliated companies, or third party partners may place a "cookie" in the browser files of a user's computer. The cookie itself does not contain any personally identifying information, except when such information has been supplied by a subscriber or registered user. 

If you have registered with NaijaDailies.com, the information in your "cookie" is used to provide a more personalized experience on our Web site. 

If you haven't registered with our site, we may place a cookie on your system to help provide a more personalized experience on NaijaDailies.com. This cookie identifies you as a unique user by means of a tracking ID. However, if you have not registered on our site, we cannot link that user ID with personal identifying information and data about you such as your name or e-mail address. 

Other cookies without personally identifying information and data are used to enable NaijaDailies.com to manage the news feed options or personalized information to the user. 

Browsers or third-party software can allow you to block the use of cookies while you surf our site. Or, you can use third-party "anonymizer" services to mask information in your cookies, or even general data such as your IP address. In such cases you would not be able to take advantage of most of the personalization services offered by NaijaDailies.com. 

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website. 

Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. 

You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the [ads preference manager](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).) 

The aggregated information we collect is used for a number of purposes including the following: 

  1. to improve the content and design of the NaijaDailies.com web site
  2. to enable our audit unit to verify our claims of traffic to the site
  3. to help advertisers, potential advertisers or marketers assess the suitability of the site for their ad campaigns
  4. as clear GIFs, also known as pixel tags, provided by our ad-serving company to help manage online advertising. These clear GIFs let our ad-serving company recognize a browser's cookie when a user visits our site. The information we collect and share through this technology is not personally identifiable (It does not include your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address).
  5. NaijaDailies.com has contracted with third party online ad company to serve all advertising on www.naijadailies.com, both on the web site itself and through its e-mail newsletters. When the company is serving ads, it recognizes certain types of non-personally identifiable information, such as a user's IP address, browser version or type, operating system, service provider and time zone. The company also uses cookies to note the general content of the sites that users visit over time in order to serve ads on this site and other sites. Any pages a user calls up on NaijaDailies.com aren't connected with personally identifiable information collected either at the NaijaDailies.com site or elsewhere. We use web metric vendors to gather information to help us understand how users utilize our websites and other electronic products.
  6. We may create and use aggregate customer data to understand more about the interests of our customers and may use the data to offer goods and services we believe may be of interest to our customers, on behalf of NaijaDailies.com, its sister Zeemfa companies, or select organizations.

Postal addresses, and other personally identifying information and data will be used to promote NaijaDailies.com and other Zeemfa companies' products and services, and may be rented and/or licensed to selected outside firms for promotional purposes. Offers for which the personally identifying information and data are rented and/or licensed for use and the users are required to target their offers carefully. 

Residential telephone numbers of NaijaDailies.com subscribers are used by NaijaDailies.com to collect re-qualification data and may be used by NaijaDailies.com, Zeemfa and other Zeemfa companies, affiliates and it's advertisers for promotional purposes. NaijaDailies.com may rent and/or license for use phone numbers to selected outside firms for promotional purposes. Offers for which the numbers are rented and/or licensed for use are required to target their offers carefully. 

Mobile telephone numbers that are provided to NaijaDailies.com will be used to provide the products and services you've specifically requested, such as, but not limited to content delivery via sms text or other technologies, and for customer service related to the products and services you've requested. With your express consent, your mobile telephone number may be used to promote other products and services of NaijaDailies.com, as well as the products and services of other Zeemfa companies. Further, your mobile phone number may, with your express consent, be used to promote the products and services of carefully chosen third parties. At any time you may "opt-out" of receiving communications via your mobile phone from NaijaDailies.com, other Zeemfa companies, and third parties, by clicking the unsubscribe link of any individual message you may receive. Because many phone companies recycle phone numbers, it is possible for users who purchase a new phone to receive messages that the previous owner had subscribed to or otherwise consented to receive. 

Fax numbers of NaijaDailies.com subscribers are used by NaijaDailies.com to collect re-qualification data and may be used for surveys for NaijaDailies.com and third parties. Except as set forth in this policy no fax numbers are rented and/or licensed to outside firms. 

E-mail addresses of NaijaDailies.com subscribers are used for re-qualification purposes. These e-mail addresses may also be used to collect feedback by members of our editorial or research team, to promote NaijaDailies.com and Zeemfa products and services, and they may be rented to other firms and/or licensed for promotional purposes. When you provide your email address to us, you agree to receive email from NaijaDailies.com and its sister Zeemfa companies. We allow users to "opt-out" of receiving e-mail from outside firms, however, when e-mail information is collected and with each e-mail use of the user's address you can individually “opt-out” of receiving further e-mail from outside firms, NaijaDailies.com and its sister Zeemfa companies. If a user does not choose to “opt-out” at the time the e-mail address is collected, or does not respond to the questions concerning how we may use their email address, the address may be rented and/or licensed for use to outside firms. Offers for which the e-mail address is rented and/or licensed for use require the users to target their offers carefully. 

Users who later decide they want to change their preferences may do so at https://www.naijadailies.com/. 

Personal identifying information submitted on portions of our site developed with outside third parties may be shared with those third parties, and the information will be governed by those parties' privacy policies as well as NaijaDailies.com's. NaijaDailies.com, nor any of its parent companies or any of its subsidiaries or affiliates do not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of such third parties. 

Credit or debit cardholders who transact with them on NaijaDailies.com will not have their privacy violated in anyway. 

NaijaDailies.com users should be aware that when they disclose personal identifying information (e.g., user name, address, company name, telephone number, demographic information, buying information, other data and E-mail address) in discussion forums, chat rooms or other areas that are publicly accessible by others, that information can be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages from other posters or parties. NaijaDailies.com nor its parent company or any of its subsidiaries or affiliates are not responsible for any information that you provide in the above areas. 

In the event that part or all of the ownership of NaijaDailies.com or any of its products are sold or transferred, all lists and data which contains personally identifying information and data including for example user name, address, company name, telephone number, demographic information, buying information, other data and e-mail address, will be transferred to the new owner.
